{
    "subject": "Lady_Jane_Grey",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Lord_Guilford_Dudley",
    "human_readable": "Lady Jane Grey is married to Lord Guilford Dudley.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9885089993476868,
            "question": "Is there a known marriage between Lady Jane Grey and Lord Guilford Dudley?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9877299666404724,
            "question": "Who were the spouses of Lady Jane Grey and Lord Guilford Dudley?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9650971293449402,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Lady Jane Grey and Lord Guilford Dudley?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9056953191757202,
            "question": "Was Lady Jane Grey married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.901781439781189,
            "question": "Who is Lady Jane Grey married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8612793684005737,
            "question": "To whom was Lady Jane Grey wed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7817817330360413,
            "question": "Who was Lady Jane Grey's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7543274164199829,
            "question": "What is the name of Lord Guilford Dudley's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7168101072311401,
            "question": "Can you provide information about the marriage of Lady Jane Grey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.712672233581543,
            "question": "What was the marital status of Lord Guilford Dudley?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lady Jane Grey is married to Lord Guilford Dudley.",
            "html": "yago_30416_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide information about the marriage of Lady Jane Grey?",
            "html": "yago_30416_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Lord Guilford Dudley's wife?",
            "html": "yago_30416_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was Lady Jane Grey's husband?",
            "html": "yago_30416_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30416_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30416_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30416_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30416_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30416_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30416_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30416_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30416_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30416_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30416_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis indicates that the information in the documents supports the triple, i.e., the statement that Lady Jane Grey is married to Lord Guilford Dudley is correct according to the provided context."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Lady Jane Grey was married to Lord Guildford Dudley. Additional details provided in the context confirm this marriage and give further information about their ages at the time of marriage, the nobility's attendance, and other related events."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}